https://www.uvawise.edu/privacy-statement/

UVA Wise Privacy Statement
Skip to content
Search for:
A-Z Index
Search for:
UVA Wise Public Users Information Privacy Statement
This statement was last modified on February 22, 2016.
The University of Virginia’s College at Wise, aka UVA Wise, owns and maintains the website, www.uvawise.edu (Site). We value our website visitors and their information and will only use your Personal Information for statistical and contact purposes as indicated. By using the Site and/or providing the requested Personal Information, you agree to the collection and use of this information in accordance with this statement. Additional rules, regulations, laws and policies may govern current students, faculty and staff using the resources of the College.
Information Collection And Use
While using the Site, we may ask you to provide us with certain personally identifiable information that can be used to contact and/or identify you. Personally identifiable information may include, but is not limited to your name, mailing address, email address and phone number (“Personal Information”).
Log Data
Like many site operators, we collect information that your browser sends whenever you visit our Site (“Log Data”). This Log Data may include information such as your computer’s Internet Protocol (“IP”) address, browser type, browser version, the pages of our Site that you visit, the time and date of your visit, the time spent on those pages and other statistics.
Cookies
Cookies are files with a small amount of data, which may include an anonymous unique identifier.
Cookies are sent to your browser from a web site and stored on your computer’s hard drive.
Like many sites, we use “cookies” to collect information. You can instruct your browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent. However, if you do not accept cookies, you may not be able to use some portions of our Site.
Security
The security of your Personal Information is important to us, but remember that no method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure. While we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your Personal Information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security.
Changes to This Privacy Statement
UVA Wise may update this Privacy Statement from time to time. You are advised to review this Privacy Statement periodically to ensure that you are aware of any changes.
Contact Us
If you have any questions about this Privacy Statement, please contact us:
Gateways for:
Council of Public Liberal Arts Colleges (COPLAC)
